Guide to the Creative Time Records MSS.179
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series I: Exhibitions and Projects, 1974-2012; 204.08 Linear Feet in 19 record cartons, 75 manuscript boxes, 275 jewel cases, 22 box binders, 8 oversized flat boxes, 9 oversized folders, 5 shared record cartons, 2 tall manuscript boxes, 1 half manuscript box, 1 shared flat box, and 1 shared casset
  - Tibor in Orbit by Tibor Kalman -- Co-Presented by The New Museum and Maira Kalman, May-August 2000
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Times Square (Box 147, Dvd 179.0276)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0351)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Times Square (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0275)
  - Art in the Anchorage 17: NoiseGate by Granular Synthesis, June 2000
    - Programs, Correspondence, Press, and Photographs (Box 54, Folder 3-5, Box 55, Folder 1)
    - Slides (Box 129, Folder Sleeves 29-34)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Production Footage (Box 146, Dvd 179.0188)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Production Footage (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0187)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 146, Dvd 179.0174)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0173)
  - Music in the Anchorage by Multiple Artists, June 2000
    - Programs, Correspondence, Press, and Photographs (Box 55, Folder 2-3)
    - Slides (Box 130, Folder Sleeves 5-14)
  - "The Gene Project" -- Correspondence and Proposal, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 4-5)
  - Genetic Code Copyright Certificate Project by Larry Miller -- Correspondence and Certificate, 2000 (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - DNAid: Deli Cups by Multiple Artists, July 2000
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 56, Folder 1)
    - Negatives (Box 136, Folder 8)
    - Cups (Box 102)
    - Slides (Box 130, Folder Sleeves 3-4)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Kathy Brew and Roberto Guerra (Box 147, Dvd 179.0272)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Kathy Brew and Roberto Guerra (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0271)
  - DNAid: Billboards by Multiple Artists, September 2000
    - Correspondence, Programs, Photographs, and Press (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Slides (Box 130, Folder Sleeves 15-17)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Bus Tour (Box 147, Dvd 179.0292)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Bus Tour (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0291)
  - Paradise Now by Multiple Artists -- Co-Presented by Exit Art and Gene Media Forum, September-October 2000
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Theresa Duncan and Jeremy Blake -- History of Glamour (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0676)
  - Cell Rules: The Lounge -- Part of Airtime: A Series of Wireless Art Projects by Multiple Artists -- Program, November 2000 (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Untitled, 1995 by Felix Gonzalez-Torres -- Program and Press, December 2000 (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Day With(out) Art: The Banner Project 2000 and CineVirus: Make a Scene by Multiple Artists -- Programs, Correspondence, and Photographs, December 2000 (Box 56, Folder 6, Box 57, Folder 1-2)
  - Citywide -- Guidelines and Correspondence, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - ARTificial Tree by Komar and Melamid -- Unrealized Project -- Correspondence and Proposal, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - "RETinevitable 2" -- Unrealized Project -- Correspondence and Proposal, 2000 (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - "Blur 01: New Creative Practices Within Developing Technologies" Seminars -- Co-Presented by Thundergulch, The New School, and Parsons School of Design, January 2001
    - Program and Correspondence (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Noam Toran -- Object for Lonely Men (Box 150, Dvd 179.0559)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Noam Toran -- Object for Lonely Men (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0558)
  - Clouds by Vik Muniz, February 2001
    - Correspondence, Programs, Photographs, and Press (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Slides (Box 130, Folder Sleeve 20)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Worst Possible Illusion: The Curiosity Cabinet of Vik Muniz (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0671)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Vik Muniz -- What's the Big Idea -- EGG, The Arts Show (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0678)
  - The 59th Minute by Multiple Artists -- Co-Presented by Panasonic, February-December 2001
    - Programs, Correspondence, Photographs, and Press (Box 57, Folder 8, Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Negative (Box 136, Folder 7)
    - Slides (Box 130, Folder Sleeves 22-28)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Michael Snow -- Fridge (Box 149, Dvd 179.0479)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Fischli and Weiss, Cat Drinking Milk, William Kentridge, Shadows, Bruce and Norman Yonemoto, ahistory; Jeff Gibson, Viralysis; Gary Hill, Liminal Object, Mary Lucier, Monarch, Michael Snow, Fridge, and Genevieve Cadieux, Portrait (Box 149, Dvd 179.0481)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- William Kentridge (Box 147, Dvd 179.0260)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Bruce and Norman Yonemoto -- ahistory (Box 148, Dvd 179.0348)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Gary Hill, Michael Snow, and Mary Lucier -- Fast Forward (Box 148, Dvd 179.0370)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Marco Brambilla -- Superstar (Box 148, Dvd 179.0354)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Marco Brambilla, Superstar, Fischli and Weiss, Cat Drinking Milk, and William Kentridge, Shadow (Box 147, Dvd 179.0258)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Fischli and Weiss, Cat Drinking Milk, William Kentridge, Shadows, Bruce and Norman Yonemoto, ahistory; Jeff Gibson, Viralysis; Gary Hill, Liminal Object, Mary Lucier, Monarch, Michael Snow, Fridge, and Genevieve Cadieux, Portrait (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0480)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- William Kentridge (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0259)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Bruce and Norman Yonemoto -- ahistory (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0347)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Gary Hill, Michael Snow, and Mary Lucier -- Fast Forward (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0369)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Marco Brambilla -- Superstar (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0353)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Marco Brambilla, Superstar, Fischli and Weiss, Cat Drinking Milk, and William Kentridge, Shadow (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0257)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Michael Snow -- Fridge (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0478)
  - Wink by Takashi Murakami, March-April 2001
    - Electronic Records, March-April 2001; cuid40902
    - Correspondence, Programs, Photographs, and Press (Box 58, Folder 2-3)
    - Slides (Box 130, Folder Sleeves 29-30)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Grand Central Installation (Box 145, Dvd 179.0138)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Grand Central Installation (Box 146, Dvd 179.0198)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Grand Central Installation (Box 151, Dvd 179.0627)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Grand Central Installation (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0137)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Grand Central Installation (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0197)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Grand Central Installation (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0626)
  - Art in the Anchorage 18: Massless Medium: Explorations in Sensory Immersion by Multiple Artists, May-June 2001
    - Electronic Records, May-June 2001; cuid40895
    - Correspondence, Programs, Photographs, and Press (Box 5, Folder 247, Box 58, Folder 4-5, Box 59, Folder 1-2)
    - Slides (Box 130, Folder Sleeves 31-33)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 146, Dvd 179.0172)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0171)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Honest (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0123)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Leo Villareal -- Building as Display, Megaparticle, Cloud Chamber (sound), Strobe Display, and Chase Display (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0133)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Bonnen and Phillips -- Building as Display (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0673)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Barry McGee -- Mass Destruction -- Shibuya-Ku, Tokyo -- Filmed by Cheryl Dunn (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0684)
  - Music in the Anchorage by Multiple Artists, June 2001
    - Correspondence, Programs, Photographs, and Press (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Slides (Box 130, Folder Sleeve 34)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- #3 (Box 151, Dvd 179.0623)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Rough Footage (Box 151, Dvd 179.0647)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Porter Ricks -- SND -- #3 (Box 151, Dvd 179.0619)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Porter Ricks and Thomas Heckman -- #4 (Box 151, Dvd 179.0621)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- #3 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0622)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Rough Footage (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0646)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Porter Ricks -- SND -- #3 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0618)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Porter Ricks and Thomas Heckman -- #4 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0620)
  - 4316 Watercolors by Mark Malmgren -- Co-Presented by The Downtown Alliance, December 2001
    - Correspondence, Programs, Photographs, and Press (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Slides (Box 130, Folder Sleeve 36)
  - East New York Project by Tracie Morris -- Unrealized Project -- Correspondence and Proposal, 2001 (Box 59, Folder 5, Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Listening Post by Ben Rubin and Mark Hansen -- Project Not Presented by Creative Time, 2001
    - Slides (Box 130, Folder Sleeve 18)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0661)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0662)
  - Time to Consider: The Arts Respond to 9.11 by Multiple Artists, 2002
    - Electronic Records, cuid40896
    - Programs, Correspondence, Photographs, and Press (Box 5, Folder 248, Box 60, Folder 2-3)
    - Slides (Box 130, Folder Sleeve 35, Box 131, Folder Sleeve 1)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Stephanie Simon -- "Poster Project" (Box 147, Dvd 179.0268)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Stephanie Simon -- "Poster Project" (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0267)
  - Art on the Plaza 1: Primal Graphics 2002 by Jim Campbell, February-August 2002
    - Programs, Correspondence, Press, and Photographs (Box 60, Folder 4-5, Box 61, Folder 1-2)
    - Blueprints for Potential Art Sites (Box 97, Folder 3)
    - Slides (Box 131, Folder Sleeve 2)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Jim Campbell -- Untitled (Agora) (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0205)
  - Untitled by Hans Haacke, March 2002
    - Correspondence, Programs, Press, and Photographs (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- May 12, 2001 (Box 146, Dvd 179.0246)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- May 12, 2001 (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0245)
  - Tribute in Light by Julian Laverdiere, Paul Myoda, et al., March-April 2002
    - Electronic Records, cuid40903
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 61, Folder 4-5, Box 62, Folder 1-2)
    - Photographs (Box 97, Folder 2)
    - Negatives (Box 136, Folder 9)
    - Slides (Box 131, Folder Sleeves 10-11)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Dateline -- "Out of the Ashes" (Box 149, Dvd 179.0493)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Dateline -- "Out of the Ashes" (Box 147, Dvd 179.0288)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy-- CBS Evening News -- Memorials (Box 147, Dvd 179.0282)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Tribute in Light -- Press Conference (Box 148, Dvd 179.0425)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Tribute in Light -- Anne Pasternak on Pure Oxygen (Box 150, Dvd 179.0551)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Tribute in Light -- Nippon Television Coverage -- Tokyo (Box 148, Dvd 179.0423)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Tribute in Light -- Nippon Television Coverage -- Tokyo (Box 150, Dvd 179.0547)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Tribute in Light -- Press Conference -- Part 2 (Box 150, Dvd 179.0549)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Tribute in Light -- Pure Oxygen -- Segment B (Box 149, Dvd 179.0427)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Tribute in Light -- CNN Coverage (Box 150, Dvd 179.0545)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Tribute in Light -- Illumina TV -- "ArtsWorld" (Box 149, Dvd 179.0495)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Tribute in Light -- NY1 Coverage (Box 149, Dvd 179.0497)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Tribute in Light -- Proun Space Studio (Box 149, Dvd 179.0499)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Therese Cafaro and Jayson Haedrich -- Tribute: A Documentary (Box 148, Dvd 179.0421)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Dateline -- "Out of the Ashes" (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0492)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Dateline -- "Out of the Ashes" (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0287)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- CBS Evening News -- Memorials (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0281)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Tribute in Light -- Press Conference (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0424)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Tribute in Light -- Anne Pasternak on Pure Oxygen (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0550)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Tribute in Light -- Nippon Television Coverage -- Tokyo (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0422)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Tribute in Light -- Nippon Television Coverage -- Tokyo (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0546)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Tribute in Light -- Press Conference -- Part 2 (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0548)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Tribute in Light -- Pure Oxygen -- Segment B (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0426)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Tribute in Light -- CNN Coverage (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0544)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Tribute in Light -- Illumina TV -- "ArtsWorld" (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0494)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Tribute in Light -- NY1 Coverage (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0496)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Tribute in Light -- Proun Space Studio (Box 29, Folder ID: 179.0498)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Therese Cafaro and Jayson Haedrich -- Tribute: A Documentary (Box 30, Folder ID: 179.0672)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Therese Cafaro and Jayson Haedrich -- Tribute: A Documentary (Box 28, Folder ID: 179.0420)
  - Tap by James Buckhouse, Holly Brubach, et al. -- Co-Presented by Dia Center for the Arts, March-July 2002
    - Correspondence, Programs, Press, and Photographs (Box 62, Folder 3-4)
    - Slides (Box 131, Folder Sleeve 12)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- 30 Second Spot on Tech TV (Box 147, Dvd 179.0284)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- 30 Second Spot on Tech TV (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0283)
  - "Blur 02: Power at Play in Digital Art and Culture" -- Co-Presented by The New School, April 2002
    - Electronic Records, cuid40904
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 62, Folder 5, Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Slides (Box 131, Folder Sleeve 13)
  - Wireless New York: Digital Happy Hour at the Kitchen -- Co-Presented by Eyebeam Atelier, April 2002
    - Program (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0175)
  - Metapet by Natalie Bookchin and Action Tank, April 2002
    - Programs, Correspondence, and Press (Box 63, Folder 3-4)
    - Slides (Box 131, Folder Sleeve 15)
  - Consuming Places by Multiple Artists, August-October 2002
    - Electronic Records, August-October 2002; cuid40905
    - Correspondence, Programs, Press, and Photographs (Box 63, Folder 5-6, Box 64, Folder 1-3)
    - Poster (Flat-file-folder 10)
    - Slides (Box 130, Folder Sleeve 19, Box 131, Folder Sleeves 5-6)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Marjetica Potrc -- Borders -- Tape 1 (Box 146, Dvd 179.0180)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Marjetica Potrc -- Borders -- Tape 2 (Box 151, Dvd 179.0629)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Marjetica Potrc -- Borders -- Tape 1 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0179)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Marjetica Potrc -- Borders -- Tape 2 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0628)
  - Focus on Peace by Nancy Burson -- Co-Presented with the Lower Manhattan Cultural Council, September 2002
    - Postcard (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Slides (Box 131, Folder Sleeve 4)
  - Garlic=Rich Air by Shu Lea Cheang -- Postcard, September 2002 (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Music in DUMBO 2002 by Multiple Artists, September-October 2002
    - Program and Press (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Slides (Box 131, Folder Sleeves 7-9)
  - Sonic Garden by Multiple Artists, October-November 2002
    - Electronic Records, cuid40906
    - Correspondence, Programs, Press, and Photographs (Box 64, Folder 7, Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- NY Tonight Coverage (Box 147, Dvd 179.0296)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- NY Tonight Coverage (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0295)
  - Art on the Plaza 2: Back of a Snowman by Gary Hume, October 2002-April 2003
    - Electronic Records, cuid40907
    - Correspondence, Programs, Press, and Photographs (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - The 59th Minute by Geneviève Cadieux and William Wegman, November 2002-January 2003
    - Programs, Press, Photographs, and Correspondence (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Slides (Box 131, Folder Sleeve 3)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Geneviève Cadieux -- Portrait (Box 147, Dvd 179.0280)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Fox Good Day Live -- William Wegman (Box 148, Dvd 179.0374)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Geneviève Cadieux -- Portrait (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0279)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Fox Good Day Live -- William Wegman (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0373)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- William Wegman -- Dog Duet, 2003 (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0401)
  - Holiday Light Show at Grand Central Terminal by Multiple Artists -- Co-Presented by Metropolitan Transit Authority (MTA), Häagen Dazs, and Scharff Weisberg, November-December 2002
    - Electronic Records, cuid40908
    - Programs, Press, and Correspondence (Box 65, Folder 4-5)
    - Prints (Box 136, Folder 10)
    - Slides (Box 131, Folder Sleeve 16)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Compilation Reel (Box 147, Dvd 179.0286)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Compilation Reel (Box 24, Folder ID: 179.0285)
  - "The New Time Square Art Project" -- Proposal for the Times Square Business Improvement District, 2002-2003 (Box 66, Folder 1)
  - Bioluminescent Beacon by Julian Laverdiere and Paul Myoda -- Unrealized Project -- Correspondence and Proposal, 2002 (Box 66, Folder 2-3)
  - Citywide -- Guidelines and Correspondence, 2003 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  - The 59th Minute by Thomas Struth -- Co-Presented by Panasonic and the Metropolitan Museum of Art, February-May 2003
    - Programs, Press, Correspondence, and Photographs (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Slides (Box 131, Folder Sleeve 14)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 148, Dvd 179.0386)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- "Video Portraits: Kim Heirston, Thomas Gutt, Anne Grefe, Rafael Hartmann" (Box 151, Dvd 179.0607)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Thomas Struth Exhibit -- German Television (Box 148, Dvd 179.0362)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0385)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- "Video Portraits: Kim Heirston, Thomas Gutt, Anne Grefe, Rafael Hartmann" (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0606)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Thomas Struth Exhibit -- German Television (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0361)
  - The Armory Show by Multiple Artists -- Co-Presented by Häagen-Dazs' "Art of Pure Pleasure" Program, March 2003
    - Programs, Press, and Correspondence (Box 66, Folder 6, Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Pennants by Kim Bennett (Box 97, Folder 4)
  - The Peace Piece by Adelle Lutz [with Courtney Harmel and Sara Driver in 2004], March 2003
    - Electronic Records, cuid40868
    - Programs, Correspondence, Photographs, and Press (Box 5, Folder 250, Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy (Box 151, Dvd 179.0605)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Courtney Harmel -- Brooklyn Library Projections, November 1999 (Box 146, Dvd 179.0194)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Courtney Harmel -- Brooklyn Library Projections, November 1999 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0193)
    - Video Recording -- Original (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0604)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Brooklyn Library (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0183)
  - What Is What by Bill Shannon, March 2003
    - Programs and Press (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Bill Shannon -- "Axis Dance and Solo" (Box 148, Dvd 179.0368)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Bill Shannon -- "Axis Dance and Solo" (Box 27, Folder ID: 179.0367)
  - "Blur 03: Projects and Prototypes" by Giles Lane -- Co-Presented by The New School and Parsons School of Design -- Program, April 2003 (Box 67, Folder 4)
  - Local Frequencies by Gabri Christa, Toshi Reagon, and Everton Sylvester, May 2003
    - Electronic Records, cuid40909
    - Correspondence, Programs, Press, and Photographs (Box 67, Folder 5-6)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Toshi -- 8/28/02 -- 1 of 2 (Box 151, Dvd 179.0633)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Toshi -- 8/28/02 -- 2 of 2 (Box 151, Dvd 179.0617)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Everton Sylvester -- Skylight Gallery -- 9/5/02 -- Tape 1 (Box 151, Dvd 179.0641)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Everton Sylvester -- Skylight Gallery -- 9/5/02 -- Tape 2 (Box 145, Dvd 179.0154)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Everton Sylvester -- Skylight Gallery -- 9/5/02 -- Tape 3 (Box 151, Dvd 179.0631)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Everton Sylvester -- Skylight Gallery -- 9/5/02 -- Tape 4 (Box 146, Dvd 179.0166)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Gabri SI High School -- 9/13/02 -- Part 1 of 2 (Box 151, Dvd 179.0649)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Gabri SI High School -- 9/13/02 -- Part 2 of 2 (Box 151, Dvd 179.0615)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Toshi -- 8/28/02 -- 1 of 2 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0632)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Toshi -- 8/28/02 -- 2 of 2 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0616)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Gabri SI High School -- 9/13/02 -- Part 1 of 2 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0648)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Gabri SI High School -- 9/13/02 -- Part 2 of 2 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0614)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Everton Sylvester -- Skylight Gallery -- 9/5/02 -- Tape 1 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0640)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Everton Sylvester -- Skylight Gallery -- 9/5/02 -- Tape 2 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0153)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Everton Sylvester -- Skylight Gallery -- 9/5/02 -- Tape 3 (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0630)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Everton Sylvester -- Skylight Gallery -- 9/5/02 -- Tape 4 (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0165)
  - Matrix X by Erwin Redl -- Co-Presented by Häagen-Dazs' "Art of Pure Pleasure" Program at Art Chicago 2003, May 2003
    - Electronic Records, May 2003; cuid40910
    - Correspondence, Press, and Programs (Box 68, Folder 1)
  - The 59th Minute by Jeremy Blake -- Correspondence and Press, July-September 2003 (Box 68, Folder 2)
  - Light Cycle by Cai Guo-Qiang -- Co-Presented by Häagen-Dazs, the City of New York, and the Central Park Conservancy, September 2003
    - Correspondence, Programs, Press, and Photographs (Box 68, Folder 3-5)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Cai Guo-Qiang -- Gunpowder -- Drawings at Grucci (Box 151, Dvd 179.0635)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Light Cycle (Box 147, Dvd 179.0274)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Light Cycle (Box 151, Dvd 179.0637)
    - Video Recording -- Access Copy -- Light Cycle and Aerial (Box 146, Dvd 179.0190)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Cai Guo-Qiang -- Gunpowder -- Drawings at Grucci (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0634)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Light Cycle (Box 25, Folder ID: 179.0273)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Light Cycle (Box 31, Folder ID: 179.0636)
    - Video Recording -- Original -- Light Cycle and Aerial (Box 26, Folder ID: 179.0189)